They broke every rule, loved every woman, took every risk and solved the most shocking murder
in the history of Beverly Hills. And it's all true. Give or take a lie or two.
Sunset is a crime, mystery, thriller film directed by Blake Edwards.
Tom Mix and Wyatt Earp team up to solve a murder at
the Academy Awards in 1929 Hollywood.
Wyatt Earp, played by James Garner.
Tom Mix, played by Bruce Willis.
Alfie Alperin, played by Malcolm McDowell.
Cheryl King, played by Mariel Hemingway.
Nancy Shoemaker, played by Kathleen Quinlan.
Victoria Alperin, played by Jennifer Edwards.
Sunset is a 1988 American mystery western film written and directed by Blake Edwards and starring Bruce Willis as Western actor
Tom Mix, who teams up with lawman Wyatt Earp, portrayed for the second time in a theatrical film by James Garner.
Based on an unpublished novel by Rod Amateau, the plot has Earp
and Mix solve a murder in Hollywood in 1929.
Although Sunset has some comedic elements, it veers much more
to the period mystery genre of old Hollywood.
Reviewers, such as Roger Ebert, struggled trying to define the film.
Ebert noted: "The strangest thing about Sunset is
that it's not a comedy, not exactly.
It has some laughs, but it's a sort of low-key, elegiac mood film ..."
While Willis
received top billing in Sunset, Garner had more screen time in the film.
This was the second and final film in which Garner played Wyatt Earp, the
first being John Sturges's Hour of the Gun, released in 1967.
This was director Edwards's second and final collaboration with
Willis, whom he directed in Blind Date (1987).
The film explores themes of showdown, wyatt earp, murder, western hero.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.